看到他们了吗?
do you see them anywhere?
干嘛不去他们家等呢
Why don't we go back to theirabchouse, wait for them there.
指不定敲第16次门时 他们会开
Yeah, 'cause they'll probably answerabcthe door the sixteenth time I knock.
他们在那儿
There they are.
抱歉我跟到这里
I'm sorry I followed you here.
我只求您们能给我几分钟时间
I just really wish you could giveabcme a few minutes of your time.
我知道也许你不同意公开收养
I know you would never agreeabcto make it an open adoption,
但我猜也许你们别无选择
but I just figured maybeabcyou never had a choice.
毕竟这是中国 不是吗?
I mean, it's china, right?
他说什么?
W-what did he say?
他让你别烦他们
He wants you to leave them alone.
求您了... 就十分钟
Please... I just want ten minutes.
了解你们是怎样的人 讲讲我的故事
Learn what you'reabclike,tell you about my life.
他说他没有女儿
He said they have no daughter.
抱歉你白来一趟
I am sorry you wasted a trip.
我知道就是他们
I know that's them.
这个要怎么用?
How does that work?
我要怎么祈祷?
How do I pray?
你许个愿然后把佛像举起来
You make a wish and lift the buddha.
我希望他们能明白abc我多么想和他们相认
I wish they couldabcunderstand how badly I need this.
现在再许一遍愿
Now make the wish again.
要是你这次举不起佛像了abc你的愿望就会实现
If you cannot lift the buddha thisabctime, your wish will be granted.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
我在急诊室翻了Cameron的口袋
I picked cameron's pocket down in E.R.
搞来了个极其好玩的病例
I came up with a doozy.
你妈妈打了两次电话来
Your mother called-- twice.
她身子好着呢
She's still healthy.
而这个25岁的女性却...
This 25-year-old woman,abcon the other hand...
她听上去好像有急事
her messages sounded kind of urgent.
50年的老伴死了的女人听上去都这样
Well, that's the way women soundabcwhen their spouse of 50 years dies.
你父亲过世了? 你不是...
Your dad died? Are you--
是 很好!
yep. Fine!
我们的病人时不时爱喝上几杯
our patient, who's been known toabctake a few drinks on non-occasions,
在中国旅行时呕血并昏倒
vomits blood and collapsesabcon a trip to china.
被中国的外科医生切掉了一尺的肠子
Chinese surgeons cutabcout a foot of bowel,
但是疼痛无好转反而加重
but the pain is worseabcnow than it was before.
House 回电话给你妈妈
House, call your mom.
你谁啊 我妈?
What are you, my mom?
我们可以五分钟之后继续讨论
We can continue thisabcdifferential in five minutes.
你眼睛下面那玩意儿是不是眼袋?
Are those bags under your eyes?
一宿没睡吧
You were up all night.
你跟她说了 是吗?
You told her, didn't you?
我不知道你和父亲有什么问题abc别把话题转向我
I don't know what your daddy issuesabcare, but don't deflect them on me.
他向老婆承认出轨了
Told his wife he's beenabcgetting some strange.
她把混蛋踢出了家门
She kicked his adulterousabctuchus to the curb.
真的 你真告诉她了?
Seriously, you told her?
是的 我说了
Yes, I told her.
但是她没有赶我走
But no, she did not kick me to the curb.
我们一直谈到很晚
We stayed up late talking.
而且会继续谈
We're going to continue talking.
就像House现在该对他母亲做的一样
Much like House should beabcdoing with his mother right now.
谁懂中文?
anybody read chinese?
不然怎么知道那些医生对她做了什么
Otherwise, we have no ideaabcwhat these doctors did to her.
Kutner 你不是有亚洲血统么? 翻译一下
Kutner, you're sort of asian,abcright? Get it translated.
是不是麦克尔憩室的问题?
What about meckel's diverticulum?
如果手术没有移除憩室 可以导致疼痛和出血.
If the surgeons didn't remove theabcdiverticulum, it can cause pain, bleeding.
对结肠镜检而言位置太高
Too high up for a colonoscopy.
CT可能会漏掉
Ct could miss it.
超声最快
Ultrasound's fastest.
既然我是超声快手...
And since I'm fastestabcwith the ultrasound...
House 我去做超声
House, let me do the ultrasound.
你先去处理你父亲的问题 别...
You need to deal withabcyour dad and stop--
转移话题不是因为我想躲避沉重的事
I'm not deflecting becauseabcI'm avoiding something deep.
我转移话题是因为我想躲避肤浅的事
I'm deflecting because I'mabcavoiding something shallow.
说真的 我很好
Seriously, I'm fine.
我从来没喜欢过那个男人
I didn't even like the man.
没有麦克尔憩室
no meckel'S.
你去那儿是为了大米饭abc还是参加再教育夏令营?
Were you there for the riceabcor the reeducation camps?
我是去找我的生父母
I was there to track downabcmy biological parents.
就像大马哈鱼洄游到出生地一样
Like a salmon returning toabcthe stream where it was born.
那你是变完整了还是被熊吃了?
Did you become whole again,abcor did you get eaten by bears?
他们否认有我存在
They denied my existence.
四个爸妈 没有一个叫你要遮一下嘴巴
Four parents, and not one of themabctaught you to cover your mouth.
天哪! 看上去像被他们切了两半
Oh, my god! It looksabclike they cut you in half.
医生 我们是她的父母
Doctor, we're her parents.
我只是个技师
I'm just a technician.
她的医生一会就到 你等会慢慢聊
Her doctors will be byabclater. You can schmooze then.
你能不能跟他们说
Can you let them know that we, uh,
我们去了她的公寓整理了她所有的药
we went by her apartment andabccollected all her medication.
我既是技师也是医生
I'm a technician and a doctor.
你去翻我的公寓了?
You went through my apartment?
我们找到了酒
We found alcohol.
我们以为你已经戒了
We thought you'd quit.
- 是喝酒引起的吗?abc- 不是
- Did her drinking cause this?abc- No.
你能告诉她就是吗?
Can you tell her it did?
甘草
Licorice root.
谢谢不要 我很好
Uh, no, thanks. I'm good.
我扔给你是有原因的
I threw it to you for a reason.
那是她的中国医生开的
That's what the chineseabcdoctors gave her.
这东西含甘草酸
It contains glycyrrhizin.
他们把她当SARS治了?
They were treating her for sars?
不太有效
Not very effectively.
但是SARS可以解释咳嗽 导致血灌注不足abc也就解释了局部肠缺血
But sars explains the cough, causesabchypoperfusion, which explains the ischemic bowel.
好极了
It's perfect.
但是肺的症状不是很严重啊
Lung involvement isn't very severe.
那就别叫SARS叫ARS吧abc(急性呼吸系统综合症)
Okay, well, so call it "ars."
先给她用利巴韦林和干扰素
Start her on ribavirin and interferon.
听到你父亲的消息 我很难过
Sorry about your father.
我不难过
I'm not.
咱们能不能别婆婆妈妈的了?
Are we done emoting now?
要是有什么我可以做的 只要...
If there's anything Iabccan do, just--
你是对的 我今天晚上没法一个人睡
you know, you're right.I don'tabcthink I can sleep alone tonight.
你手里那是液态的维可汀吧
And you can tell meabcthat that is liquid vicodin.
我们给所有接触过那病人的人abc肌注免疫球蛋白
We're giving I.G.Shots to everyoneabcwho came in contact with your patient.
震惊的是 没有一个护士愿给你打针
Shockingly, none of the nursesabcvolunteered to administer yours.
在大块的肌肉上好些
It goes better in a large muscle.
把裤子脱了
Drop your pants.
我通常要付好几十块钱才能听到这话
You know, I usually pay tensabcof dollars to hear that.
葬礼在明天
The funeral's tomorrow.
我妈给你打电话了?
My mom called you?
有一班3:40的飞机从Newark起飞
There is a 3:40 flight out of newark.
你现在走的话 今晚就能到Lexington
If you leave now, you canabcbe in lexington tonight.
你母亲想让你致悼词
Your mother wantsabcyou to deliver a eulogy.
"悼词"来自希腊语的"好话"
"Eulogy. "From theabcgreek for "good word."
要是她让我致"混帐话"的话 我很乐意
Now, if she asked meto deliverabca bastardogy, I'd be happy to--
成熟点吧
then be a grown-up.
回电话给你妈妈 告诉她你很悲伤
Call your mother back and tellabcher that you're sick with grief,
但太忙了 去不了
but you're too busy to be there.
我撒谎的时候 她都知道
She knows when I'm lying.
那现在就开始写
Then start writing.
他们把我兄弟姐妹都从大学里叫来了
they yanked my brotherabcand sister out of college.
能不能告诉他们我没生命危险?
Can you please tell them I'm not dying?
你得了非典
You have sars.
我戴着口罩
I'm wearing a mask.
这是个挺重的病
It's a big deal.
放他们一马吧
Cut 'em some slack.
但我会没事的 对吗?
But I am gonna be okay, right?
这些药就是为了让你没事
That's what all this stuff is for.
需要你在这儿和中国接触过的abc所有人的名字
We're gonna need the names and numbers ofabceveryoneyou came in contact with here and in china.
航班号 日期...
Flight numbers, dates...
那个被我咳了一身的医生...
that doctor that I coughed all over...
他没事吧?
is he gonna be all right?
目前为止还好
So far he's fine.
又来了
It's back.
就是这样疼起来的
This is where the pain all started.
她心动过速 推个监护车过来!
She's tachycardic. Getabca crash cart in here!
怎么了? 告诉我abc怎么了! 那是我的女儿
What's going on? I need to knowabcwhat's going on. That's my daughter.
肝衰竭 不是非典
Her liver's failing. It's not sars.
我这么做 不是因为我在乎
I am not doing this because I care.
Cuddy给我下药了 她...
Cuddy drugged me. She...
我妈没给Cuddy打电话 打给了你
my mom didn't callabcCuddy. She called you.
我知道你不能置之不理
I knew you couldn't stay away.
我知道你太爱我了
I knew you loved me too much.
我是为了你母亲才这么做的
I'm doing this for your mom.
我坚决不这么做
I'm not doing this at all.
如果我要做什么abc我就会趁他快死的那几年做了
If there were something to be done, I wouldabchave done it in the year he spent dying.
你拿走了我的维可汀?
You took my vicodin?
我很痛唉
I'm in pain.
就一粒?
One?
药就是我的缰绳
So the vicodin is my leash.
一粒缓解疼痛abc但无法支持我逃回医院
One'll take the edge off, but it won't giveabcme enough relief for an escape back to plainsboro.
我的手机呢?
Where's my phone?
那是我的队 他们的专用铃声
That's the team. It's their ring tone.
管他呢
Forget it.
病人死在你手上
The patient's blood is on your hands.
House? 在吗?
House? You there?
我被绑架了 快打电话给警察!
I'm being held againstabcmy will. Call the police!
Nicole的肝静脉中有个栓子
Nicole had a clot in the hepatic vein.
Chase取出了栓子 保住了她的肝
Chase sucked it out,saved her liver.
没有肿瘤或是静脉畸形的迹象
No signs of a tumor orabcvenous malformations.
- 没什么可以导致...abc- 她是个成瘾者
- Nothing that couldabccause-- - she's an addict.
- 药物和酒精都不能...abc- 她抽烟
- Drugs and alcoholabcwouldn't-- - she's a smoker.
抽烟再加上任何一项遗传因素abc她就是个血栓制造器
Combine smoking with any one of a dozen geneticabcdisorders, and she's a clotting machine.
多发的血栓可以解释肠缺血及肺和肝的症状
Multiple blood clots would tie togetherabcbowel ischemia, lungs, and the liver.
要找到她缺什么凝血因子abc就能给她用相应的抗凝剂了
we need to pinpoint which defect she has soabcwe can start her on the right anticoagulant.
抽血检查abc看看她的生父母给了什么样的基因大礼
Draw her blood--let's find out whichabcgenetic gift her genetic parents gave her.
谢谢来电
Thanks for calling.
你的来电铃声是ABBA的舞蹈皇后
My ring tone for you isabcdancing queen, by abba.
Nicole?
我要撒尿 下一站靠边停车
I need to pee. Pullabcover at the next stop.
我直接尿在地上就行了
I'll just pee on the floor.
你买二手的脚垫?
You bought used floor mats?
太有才了
That is brilliant.
五英里处有个休息区
There's a rest stop in five miles.
拐棍
Cane.
洗手间就在那儿 你自己能行
The restroom's right there.abcYou can make it on your own.
我觉得该说说那个暑假abc他决定不跟我说一句话
I suppose I could talk about the summerabche decided he wasn't speaking to me.
两个月 一个字都没有
Two months,not one word.
他把他想说的话 打出来塞到我卧室门缝
Anything he wanted to say,he typedabcup and slipped under my bedroom door.
你什么都不想说 那就不说 但是你要去
You don't want to sayabcanything,don't say anything, but go.
告诉你妈妈 你为她而难过
Tell your mom you're sad for her.
待在那里 我就是在撒谎
Just by being there,I'd be lying.
让她觉得她曾拥有过快乐的家abc一刻就足矣
She wants to think,for a moment,abcthat she had a happy family.
给她这个礼物--撒谎又怎样!
So give herabca gift--lie!
把我的拐棍给我...
Give me my cane...
我去参加那该死的葬礼
I'll go to the damn funeral.
我说去参加葬礼 又没说什么时候
I said I'd go to theabcfuneral. I didn't say when.
有两个区域: 病房里和病房外
We have these twoabccategories:Inside and outside.
病人都要呆在病房里
Patients stay inside.
直到身体好了 才允许他们出来透透气
Then, when they're better,weabclet them go outside.
谢谢 但是在病房不允许抽烟
Thanks. But theyabcdon'tlet you smoke inside.
何不你先回去 让我再呆上五分钟?
So why don't you go back thereabcand give me five minutes outside?
握拳
Make a fist.
天气多好啊 我们今天在户外行医
'Sit such a beautiful day, we thoughtabcwe'd do all our doctoring outside.
每次我和家人出门 人们都会盯着我看
People stare at me anyabctime I'm out with my family.
就像个谜语一样
It's like a puzzle.
"猜猜哪个不是亲生的"
"Which one of theseabcthings doesn't belong?"
你把血缘看得太重了
Belonging's overrated.
我九岁的时候被白人家庭收养了
I was adopted by a whiteabcfamily when I was nine.
我喜欢与众不同
I like being different.
从外面看过来风景更好
The view's better fromabcthe outside looking in.
做个与众不同的好孩子一定容易许多
Must be easier to beabcdifferent when you're a success.
怎么了?
Is that a problem?
这就是为什么待在病房里比较好
This is why we prefer inside.
你真在后备箱里放了不用电池的手电筒?
You actually keep a flashlight thatabcdoesn't need batteries in the trunk?
还有夹克衫 备用水 指甲刀abc牙刷 太空被...
Next to the jacket, emergency water,nailabcclippers, tooth brush,space blanket--
以备万一
when things go wrong,I like to be ready.
你能不能帮我拿一会儿手电筒?
Will you... please holdabcthe flashlight for a minute?
那不仅仅是我的车钥匙
You know, those aren't just my car keys.
我家的钥匙也在
My House keys are on there too.
钥匙链是Amber送给我的
Amber gave me that key chain.
她没有
No, she didn'T.
除非你叫她的昵称是"沃尔沃"
Not unless your petabcname for her was "volvo."
一个男人拿他过世的女友编瞎话
A man who would lie about aabcgift from a dead girl friend.
那是对付某些人幼稚 毫无意义的发脾气
Is probably responding to aabcchildish, pointless act of petulance.
对抗逮捕的行动从来意义非凡
The struggle to resist one'sabccaptors is never pointless.
抗议万岁!
Viva la resistance!
实话有些残酷 切格瓦拉(著名共产主义者)abc拖延没有用的
Well, I hate to break it to you,abcche, but simple delay won't work.
你母亲会等我们到了再开始葬礼
Your mother will hold theabcfuneral till we get there.
我父亲是个守时的人
My father was a punctualabcman, beholden to time.
迟到两分钟 没晚饭吃
Two minutes late forabcdinner,you didn't eat.
我母亲绝对不会推迟葬礼abc那可是对他的大不敬
My mother would never disrespectabchim by starting the funeral late.
显然你没有任何缺点需要改进
Yeah, yeah, you clearlyabchave no issues to work through.
行了 别找钥匙了 叫个锁匠来
Come on, forget theabckeys. Call a locksmith.
我们先到里面和卡车司机玩abc"猜猜是谁的味儿"
We'll go inside and play "guess that smell"abcwith the truckers while we're waiting.
随我加入到阴暗面吧
Join me on the dark side.
你的阴暗面结束了 House
The dark side's done,House.
我只负责把你送到你母亲面前 别的不管
I'm delivering you to yourabcmother, and that's it.
我向前看了
I have moved on.
你们觉得House会送什么abc"温柔的安慰" 还是"窝心的着想"花束?
What do you think House would send, the "gentleabccomfort" arrangement or the "warm thoughts" bouquet?
我说假如他不是混蛋的话
I mean, if he wasn't an ass.
送个巨大的棺材型饼干
Send one of those giantabccookies shaped like a coffin.
他妈妈会相信是House送的
His mom would believe it was from him.
你们想送什么就送什么
I didn't tell you soabcyou could send anything.
只想提醒下 这人跟人类的标准相去甚远
Just wanted you to know the extent to whichabcthe man is disconnected from the human race.
用了六袋冰冻血浆才止住出血
Took a six-pack ofabcffp to stop the oozing.
她既有出血又有血栓?
She's bleeding and clotting?
检出裂红细胞说明是弥散性血管内凝血abc也就是说她有癌症
Plus schistocytes on her smear meansabcit's dic, which means she's got cancer.
她还年轻 可能是白血病
She's young. It could be leukemia.
不太可能 白细胞计数正常
Normal wbc makes that less likely.
腹痛可能说明是胃肠道肿瘤
The belly pain points toward a G.I.Tumor.
House已经做过超声了
House already didan ultrasound.
但他不是在找肿瘤 去做CT
He wasn't looking forabca tumor. Go run a ct.
我不信
I don't buy it.
CT可以找到小肠的癌变 但是超声...
Ct can find small intestinalabccancers that an ultrasound--
我不信House无动于衷
I don't buy House.
我爸爸去世时 虽然我恨他abc但我慌得害死了一个病人
When my father died,I wound upabckilling a patient. And I hated the man.
不管House如何嘴硬abc我肯定他已经六神无主了
Whatever House says or doesn'tabcsay, I'm sure the guy's a mess.
即便他是混蛋 还是你父亲
So he was a bastard. Heabcwas still your father.
你们在生理上的联系abc决定了你对他有感情
You're biologically programmed toabchave feelings for him.
不 我没有
No, I'm not.
感情不能用理性衡量
Feelings aren't rational.
我知道你无法接受不能量化的事物
I know you have trouble with anythingabcthat can't be quantified and counted.
他不是我亲生爸爸
He's not my biological father.
我12岁时就发现了
I figured it out when I was 12.
当然咯
Of course.
你12岁时已是这般遗世独立了
You were a brilliant,sociallyabcisolated 12-year-old,
于是你臆想出另一个世界abc好让你的人生不那么糟糕
and you create a parallel universeabcin which your life doesn't suck.
我有事实为据
I look at the facts.
首先 我妈妈怀我时abc他被派遣到冲绳训练
First of all, he was deployed on training exercisesabcoff okinawa during the time I had to be conceived.
鉴于你已经150岁了abc他当年没有飞机可以坐回来
And since you're 150 yearsabcold, air travel was impossible.
他的第二根脚趾比脚趾头长
His second toe isabclonger than his big toe.
而我的不是
Mine isn't.
真可悲 你竟怀疑你妈在外面乱搞--
This is sad. You don'tabcbelieve your mother screwed around--
我头皮上有块特别的胎记abc我妈有个朋友也有这么一块
I have a distinctivered birthmark on my scalpabcthat matches a certain friend of the family.
假如你相信这是真的abc你就不会说胎记了
If you believed this story, you wouldn'tabcbe telling me about his birthmarks.
而是基因测试的结果
You'd be telling me about theabcgenetic testing you had done.
既然你没提 显然是你还没做
And sinceyou haven't mentionedabcit, obviously, you didn't do it.
因为你不想-- House 你想干吗?
Because you don't wantabcto--House, what are you doing?
把你的-- 拿开 有警察!
Get your--get offabcthe-- there's a cop!
Nicole 躺着别动 只要几秒就好
Nicole, lie still. This'llabconly take a few seconds.
在上腹切开1毫米
one millimeter cutabcthrough upper abdomen.
养父母当时以为自己不能生育 收养了她
She was adopted when the parentsabcthought they couldn't have kids.
后来他们又有了三个孩子
Then they had three more.
她把这一切理解为abc"谢谢参与 但我们有自己的孩子了"
She took the message as "thanks forabcplaying, but we have our real children now."
然而在亲生孩子看来abc自己的降生是意外 她才是父母亲手挑选的
And the real children probably thinkabcthey're accidents while she was hand-picked.
每个人都对父母不满
Everybody's gotabcproblems with their parents.
但她成了瘾君子abc一定出了什么问题
She's an addict. Something went wrong.
一定是父母的问题吗? 把胰腺部分放大
And it has to be theabcparents? Magnifying pancreas.
我没说是父母的错
I'm not saying the parents screwed up.
你说的是你喜欢她
You're saying you like her.
所以你不希望这是她的错
So you don't want herabcfaults to be her fault.
但总归是某个人的错abc然而除了她 你只认识--
But they're someone's fault, andabcthe only other people you know are--
看来我们又得找House了
I think we may need to call House again.
你一不小心开快了?
you lost track of your speed?
这简直是希特勒式的借口
I think that was hitler's excuse.
一不小心杀了无数犹太人
Lost track of the jews.
结果没人追究他责任
No one held him responsible.
我不想开玩笑 House
I'm not playing House.
你想保护我
You were protecting me.
换作正常人都会把我捅出来
Anybody in their right mindabcwould have ratted me out.
我只想尽快解决问题
I'm just trying to speed things along.
你一定得出席葬礼
You are going to this funeral.
有话快说
Make it fast.
我可不想错过搜查肛门的镜头
I don't want to miss theabcanal cavity search.
似乎胰腺里有个肿块
Looks like a mass in the pancreas.
我可看不到 这是无线通信abc我要详细的描述
Not to me. This is radio.abcAnd I want a full play-by-play.
有大量积液
It's fluid-filled.
麻烦你下车好吗 先生?
Would you get out ofabcthe car, please, sir?
长官 如果你想给我开罚单abc我完全接受
Officer, if you want to give meabca ticket, I totally understand.
给我下车 先生
Just get out of the car, sir.
囊肿?
Cyst?
很大的囊肿 你那边出什么事了?
large cyst. Something going on there?
Wilson被捕了 有多大?
Wilson's getting arrested. how large?
运动车还是中型轿车那么大?
suv sized,or mid-range sedan?
真的 你们干了什么?
Seriously? What'd you do?
显然我在开玩笑
I'm obviously joking.
要是Wilson被拷上手铐摁到了车头盖上abc我还能气定神闲地做鉴别诊断吗?
If wilson was getting handcuffed on the hood ofabchis car, would I be carrying on a differential?
直径至少8厘米
Diameter is at least eight centimeters.
在胰头部还是尾部
Is it in the tailor in the head?
头部
the head.
你也是 先生 下车
You too, sir. Out of the car.
我们有块建筑工地
We've got a construction site.
一台压路机正在--
A steamrollerabcis plowing--
马上
out now.
不能拿拐杖
No cane.
James Evan Wilsonabc路易斯安那州曾对你发出拘捕令
james evan wilson, there's aabcwarrant for your arrest in louisiana.
压路机代表什么? 威力abc也许是胰腺癌
what are the traits of a steamroller?abcPowerful. Maybe pancreatic cancer.
好提议abc但能解释的症状只有好似压路机般
Great idea,except the only symptom itabcmatches up with is being steamrollerish.
你不觉得House想到什么了吗?
You don't think House is onto something?
我相信他已经有了主意
I think he thought he had an idea.
但我也相信破译他没说完整的隐喻abc不知有多困难
I also think his metaphors are toughabcenough to decipher after he's said them.
把精力集中在医学问题上
We need to be focusing on the medicine.
无人接听
No answer.
没人会接电话 他们被捕了
There's not gonna beanabcanswer. They've been arrested.
他在说笑
He was joking.
既然他关心肿瘤的尺寸和位置
He reacted to the size and location.
我们就注意这些
That's what we should be focusing on.
而不是在病人岌岌可危的时候abc还在玩什么字谜游戏
Not playing mad libs while our patient's explodingabcnoun destroys her life-sustaining noun.
我打给Wilson
I'll try to get wilsonon the line.
会不会不是指压路机的特征abc而是它的作用?
What if it's not how a steamrollerabcworks, but what it does?
清除障碍
Clears things.
简直浪费时间
This is a waste of time.
我得接电话
I need that phone call.
我是医生 当有人给我连打仨电话
I'm a doctor, and when someoneabctries to call you three times,
就是个暗号abc代表"赶紧接电话 不然有人要挂了"
it's code for "pick up the damnabcphone before someone dies."
我相信医院还有别的好医生
I'm sure there's other smart doctors.
说出来吓你一跳
You'd be surprised.
你说你已经搞定了
You told me you'd taken care of this.
的确
I did.
这是你对我说的第一句话
First words you ever said to me.
我搞定了
I took care of it.
肯定是你搞糟的
You must've screwed up somehow.
长官
Sir?
我不是催你 但我们要去出席葬礼--
Not to hurry you, but weabcneed to be at a funeral--
在路易斯安那州警局答复前abc谁也不准走 不准接电话
nobody is going anywhere or taking anyabcphone calls till I hear back from louisiana.
这是很久前的拘捕令了
It's a really old warrant.
这东西不是有时效性的吗?
Isn't there a statute ofabclimitations on this kind of thing?
当你逃出这个州 它会持续生效
It's suspended when you flee the state.
我没有逃走 我离开了这个州
I didn't flee theabcstate. I left the state.
因为我不住这个州
Because I don't live in the state.
而且只是桩很小的罪名...
And the charges were just so minor...
"毁坏文物及他人财产 攻击他人"
"vandalism, destructionabcof property, assault."
我可以解释
There is a simple explanation.
当时新奥尔良有个医学大会...
There was a medicalabcconventionin new orleans...
你无需向我解释
you don't need to explain to me.
我当时刚从医学院毕业
I was fresh out of med school.
会上的人我一个不认识
I didn't know anybody at the convention.
听到他说了吗 Wilson
You heard the man,wilson.
你无需向他解释
You don't have to explain.
我不想坐在这浪费时间abc好让你逃避你爸的葬礼!
I am not gonna sit here wasting time justabcso you can avoid your father's funeral!
他是我爸
He's my father.
我有权避开他的葬礼
I have the right to avoid his funeral.
不 只要你妈在生 你就没权
Not if your mother's alive,you don't.
好吧...解释我听听
Okay... explain.
House关注8厘米这个点了吗?
did House react toabcthe eight centimeters?
他吹了一下口哨 囊肿很大abc换了谁都这么认为
He whistled. It's huge.abcAnyone would think so.
House要不是关注这点 他不会吹口哨
House doesn't whistle becauseabche's impressed.
就是说这出乎他意料
It means he wasn't expecting it.
意味着这个点让他改变了主意
It means he changedabchis mind at that point.
单一的特大囊肿排除了有扩散机制的病abc硬皮病和狼疮
a single super-sized cyst ruled out aabcdiffuse process like scleroderma or lupus.
排除了扩散abc那只剩下对胰腺本身产生影响的单一机制
Rule out diffuse process, you're stuck withabcsingle process affecting just the pancreas.
结石或者胰腺分裂症
Gallstones or pancreatic divisum.
他接着问的问题可以缩窄范围
Whatever he asked next wouldabchave narrowed that down.
他问了位置
He asked about location.
在头部是结石 尾部是分裂症
Heads it's gallstones,tailsabcit's divisum.
在头部 她得了结石
It's at the head. She's got gallstones.
那个压路机的比喻--
The steamroller meanspotholes--
悠着点 我们有结论了
relax. We got it.
你们知道她得了结石?
You figured out she's got gallstones?
我去了酒店的吧台abc想喝杯酒放松心情
I was at the hotel bar tryingabcto unwind, have a drink.
有个人不停在点唱机上播abcBilly Joel的"遗下温柔一刻"
There was this guy who kept playing billy joel'sabcleave a tender moment alone on the jukebox.
"遗下温柔一刻"是首好歌
Leave a tender moment is a good song.
很棒的歌 他反应过激了
It's a great song. He was out of line.
虽然没有"意大利餐厅往事"动听
Not as good as scenes fromabcan italian restaurant or...
我很礼貌地让他别播了
so I--I asked theabcman to stop, politely.
没错 你很礼貌地大喊
Yeah, you yelled politely.
一开始 我很礼貌地劝了几次abc但那混蛋完全没反应
I was polite the first couple of times,abcbut courtesy made no impressionon this ass.
所以我把一个酒瓶扔向镜子
So I threw a bottle into the mirror,
以表达我内心的愤懑
which successfully conveyed my message.
砸坏一面10尺高的古董镜
And smashed a ten-foot antique mirror.
在他的带动下abc两个酒客也砸起了酒杯
And set an example to two otherabcpatrons who threw shot glasses.
我和接下来的打斗一点没关系
I had nothing to do with that fight.
所谓攻击他人的指控完全不成立
The assault charge was totally bogus.
而且我赔偿了那面镜子
And I paid for the mirror.
我知道怎么一回事了
I think I have the picture.
我想 你就是那个不停播歌的人
I assume you're the guy whoabcwas playing the song.
不 我是把他保释出来的人
No, I was the guy who bailed him out.
我们就是这么认识的 我在监狱里
That's how we met. I was in jail.
你根本不认识这人 为什么要保释他?
This guy wasa total strangerabcto you, and you bailed him out?
那个会议很无聊
It was a boring convention.
得找个人陪我喝酒
Had to have somebody to drink with.
我们的友谊正是建立在这一基础上
and there's the foundationabcof our entire friendship.
要不是你某个周末无聊abc这一切根本不存在
If you hadn't been bored oneabcweekend, it wouldn't even exist.
嘿 那个会上有3000人
Hey, there were 3,000abcpeople at that convention.
你是我唯一觉得不无聊的abc这总说明了什么吧
You were the one I thought wasn'tabcboring. That says something.
这也说明了你骗我abc你根本没有替我撤销指控
It also says something that you lied toabcme about getting the charges dropped!
我找了个律师 他和警方达成了协议
I got a lawyer. He cut a deal.
你后来没找他吗?abc你不知道还要接受传讯吗?
You didn't call the guy? Youabchave to show up at the arraignment.
地球人都知道
Everybody knows that.
只有你这种成天犯事的人才会知道
Everybody with yourabcmisdemeanor experience.
你们可以走了
You can go.
什么?
What?
他是个逃犯
He--he's aabcfugitive from justice.
那故事是骗人的 他捅了别人一刀
That whole story wasabclies. He stabbed a man.
路易斯安那州不想花钱引渡你
Louisiana doesn't wantabcto pay to get you back.
别管路易斯安那了
Forget louisiana.
他在你管辖的宁静小镇上疯狂飙车
He was driving recklessly throughabcyour comatose village.
这里的人在果酱甜甜圈里放铅了?abc(铅中毒让人反应迟缓)
Do they put lead in theabcjelly doughnuts here?
做人不能忘恩负义abc赶紧去向你父亲尽孝道
Stop acting like such an ingrate andabcgo pay your respects to your father.
CT证实了是结石
The ct confirmed gallstones.
通常不会造成危险
Normally not dangerous.
几乎每个人体内都有 但有时...
Almost everyone hasabcthem. But sometimes...
- 它们会害死你abc- 没错
- they kill you?abc- Yup.
除非把它们取出来
Unless I take 'em out.
我们用腹腔镜做
We do it laproscopically.
她的尿什么时候变成棕色了?
how long has her urine been brown?
下午肾脏还是好的
Kidney's were fine this afternoon.
现在不是了
They're not now.
不是结石的问题
It's not the gallstones.
当然不是结石
well, of course it's not gallstones.
谁说是结石了?
Who thought it was gallstones?
你说了"压路机"
You said "steamroller."
我还说了"建筑工地"
I also said "construction site."
结石会导致胰腺囊肿
Gallstones could cause a pancreatic cyst.
赶紧回去吧
Just turn around.
你兜了两个小时了
The thing is two hours over already,
这是第三次经过那abc门前有个十字架着火的殖民地房子
and that's the third time we passed thatabccolonial with the cross burning out front.
我没迷路
I'm not lost.
我说的不是导致囊肿的原因
I'm not talking aboutabcwhat caused the cyst.
而是囊肿引发了这一切症状
I'm talking about what theabccyst caused. Everything.
囊肿只是症状 不是病因
Cysts are symptoms,not diagnoses.
除非这是一个多囊肿abc与其它器官相联系
Unless it's a multiple cyst,abcwith connections to other organs--
好比一台压路机
like a steamroller.
但和肾离得也太远了吧
That's a long road down to the kidneys.
我们怎么证实?
How do we prove it?
扫描看不出来
Won't be visible in a scan.
病人出现肾衰时abcChase也不能在她体内乱捣鼓
Chase isn't gonna go groping aroundabcwhen she's got kidney failure.
气泡
Bubbles.
是你新脱衣舞娘的名字?
Is that your new stripper name?
是的 我们把气泡注射入囊肿内abc并跟踪它们的去向
Yes. And also,we inject bubbles intoabcthe cyst and follow where they drift.
如果转移到别的器官 证明你是对的abc把囊肿割除 她就没事了
If they end up in the other organs, weabcknow you're right, cut it out, she's fine.
气泡可行 做个超声
Bubbles is right. Go echo.
我没有迷路
I'm not lost.
Nicole 你得躺着别动
Nicole, you gotta stay still.
我-我很紧张
I'm--I'm nervous.
你不是紧张 而是震颤性谵妄对吧?
You're not nervous.abcIt's the dts, isn't it?
我来这儿以后一滴酒都没沾过
I haven't had a drink since I got here.
感谢上帝 我们总算没错过
Good heavens,we haven'tabcmissed it after all.
像是圣诞颂歌的结尾
It's like the end of a christmas carol.
真高兴你来了
I'm so glad you're here.
看到你我才卸下了心头大石
Oh, it's a load off ofabcmy mind just to see you.
谢谢你 James
Thank you, james.
妈 你怎能推迟葬礼?
Mom, how could you delay the funeral?
宝贝 你爸爸死了abc他不会介意的
Honey, your dad is dead.abcHe's not going to care.
你想好说什么了吗?
Do you know what you're going to say?
没想好 让牧师或者他部队的兄弟...
I don't know. Just let the ministerabcor one of his buddies from the corps...
你一定得说
you're talking.
我不管你是否喜欢他
I don't care that you didn't like him.
他是你父亲 而且他很爱你
He was your father,and he loved you.
战争结束了 Greg
The war is over, greg.
就当为了我吧
Please do this for me.
别这么紧张兮兮的
Stop looking so worried.
我知道他会让我骄傲的
I know he's gonna make me proud.
我相信 你比我更了解他
I'm sure you know him better than I do.
病情已经危及了肝脏
Her liver's been compromised.
震颤性谵妄会引起她的肌肉抽搐abc注射镇静剂也不起作用
And the dts will cause her muscles toabccontinue to twitch, even under sedation.
我们必须对她全身麻醉
We need to paralyzeabcher to do this procedure.
我不想这样
I wanted to stop.
酚巴比妥昏迷不仅能让我们注入囊肿abc还可以抑止震颤
A phenobarbital coma will not only allowabcus to inject the cyst,it'll treat the dts.
当她醒来时 就不会再受戒酒后的苦
When she wakes up,sheabcwon't be in withdrawal.
我们从前看过她戒酒
We've seen her through withdrawal before.
我们看着她经历一切
We've seen her through everything.
我们支持过 也强硬过
We've been supportive,abcwe've been combative.
曾经半夜把她从酒吧抬回来
We've picked her up fromabcbars in the middle of the night.
也曾经把她留在监狱里过夜
We've let her spend the night in jail.
我以前总会说 没事的
I used to say it'd be okay.
我能挺过来
That I'd get it together.
我再也不这么说了
I don't say that anymore.
我们先让你恢复健康
Let's make you healthy.
再操心怎么让你恢复清醒
Then we'll worry about making you sober.
上帝是我的牧羊人 我不应该...
The lord is my shepherd,abcI shall not want...
我无话可说
I am not talking.
我们只是30年前共用一块地皮的陌生人
We were strangers who sharedabcsome geography 30 years ago.
对 你完全没受他的影响
Right, he had no influence on you at all.
一个对守时有严格要求的父亲
The father who wasabccompulsive about punctuality.
这是他的缺点
His issue.
我刻意避免变成我的缺点
Which I deliberately made not my issue.
却形成你的缺点
Thereby making it your issue.
就是非得迟到4个小时abc不遵守规章纪律
Compulsively showing up four hours late,abcignoring discipline,ignoring rules.
天 他也在
Oh, god, he's here.
谁?
Who's here?
你假装是你父亲的人?
The one you're pretending is your father?
选得好 他长得像Sean Connery
Nice pick. He looks like sean connery.
当你计划闹剧的时候abc你有没有跟你老爸讲
So back when you were devising thisabcfantasy, did you tell your father:
"老爸 我没认出你abc因为我选007做我老爸了"?
"Dad, I refuse to recognize your existenceabcbecause I have chosen james bond as my dad"?
措辞稍有差异
I used different words.
什么?
What?
听到孩子说 因为太恨自己abc连脑海中对父亲的形象都改变了
Hearing your own son hates you soabcmuch he's replaced you in his mind?
太糟糕了 他怎么受得了?
That's gotta suck. How did he take it?
我跟你说过了 他一个夏天没跟我说话
I already told you. He didn'tabcspeak to me for a summer.
今天大家能来 对我太重要了
It means more to me than--than Iabccan say to have all of you here today.
我们的孩子Gregory有几句话想说
And now, uh,our son gregoryabcwould like to say a few words.
Greg?
今天来了很多人
There's a lot of people here today.
有些是军队里的
Including some from the corps.
我注意到他们都跟我父亲是同一级别abc或级别更高
And I notice that every one of themabcis either my father's rank or higher.
对于这 我不感到意外
And that doesn't surprise me.
如果对一个人的考核abc是看他怎么对待下级的话
Because if the test of a man is howabche treats those he has power over,
那恐怕我父亲通不过这项考核
it was a test my father failed.
你们急迫地向这个人表达敬意
This man you're eager to pay homage to,
除了自己的观点abc他从不认同其他观点
he was incapable of admitting anyabcpoint of view but his own.
他严厉惩罚失败abc无法接受--
He punished failure, and he didabcnot accept anything less than--
但他热爱他的事业
he loved doing what he did.
他把工作看成...
He saw his work as some kind of...
神圣的使命
sacred calling.
比任何私人感情都要重要
More important than anyabcpersonal relationship.
他如果能做个好父亲的话abc也许我能做个更好的儿子
Maybe if he'd been a betterabcfather, I'd be a better son.
但我之所以变成现在的我abc受他的影响很深
But I am what I am because of him...
不论是好的还是坏的影响
for better or for worse.
可我还是希望--
And I just--I just wish--
放回去
Put it back.
他又不会抗议
Well, he's not gonna miss it.
我不能再纵容你
I'm done enabling.
连让你父亲入土为安abc都要依着你的时间表
You can't even let them put him in theabcground without making it serve your agenda?
你一定得在大庭广众闹别扭么?
you really want to doabcthis in front of everybody?
你这是惩罚我还是他们?
You wanna punish me or them?
我居然还能感到意外
How can I still feel surprise?
你竟然把表达哀悼的仪式变成一场闹剧
You would take,even this, a moment ofabcreal human grief, and turn it into a farce.
得了吧
Oh, cut the crap.
你享受我的所作所为
You enjoy what I do.
我甚至不用逼你
I never had to force you.
你乐颠颠地送我来
You like coming along for the ride.
是啊 所以现在我为你喝彩
Yes, that's why I'm cheering you on now.
你需要不断应对最糟糕的场面
This is about you needing toabcbe prepared for the worst.
所以你当肿瘤学家
So you become an oncologist.
不出意料在肿瘤科abc最糟糕的情形从不间断
No surprises there. Worstabchappens all the time.
但Amber年轻健康
But amber, she was young and healthy.
她的死突如其来
Her death came out of nowhere.
别把Amber扯进来
Don't bring amber into this.
让你措手不及 所以你怒不可遏
And you weren't ready.abcThat makes you angry.
世界垮了 你无法振作
The world sucks, and youabcdidn't have time to brace yourself.
刚刚是你在上演闹剧
What happened out there is your show!
你害怕失去重要的人
You're scared to death ofabclosing anyone that matters.
所以宁愿抛弃最重要的人
So you dump the person whoabcmatters the most to you!
我不是害怕 我是开始新生活
I'm not scared to death.abcI'm moving forward!
只有你失去的东西 才没人能够夺走
Because no one can take awayabcfrom you what you no longer have.
你父亲的死是关于你
Your father's death is about you.
Amber的死也关于你
Amber's death is about you.
我纳闷为什么没人愿做你的朋友
I can't imagine why someone wouldn'tabcwant to be your friend!
承认吧 你生气 害怕abc是担心失去我
Admit it, you're angry andabcyou're scared of losing me.
- 我没有生气 也不害怕abc- 承认
- I'm not angry, I'm not scared.abc- Admit it.
- 我没有担心abc- 承认
- I'm not afraid.abc- Admit it.
- 我失去过亲人 这时有发生abc- 承认吧 承认吧
- I've lost people. It happens.abc- Admit it. Admit it!
你几岁 五岁? 不要重复了
What are you,five? Stop repeating--
承认吧 承认吧 承认吧abc承认吧 承认吧 承认吧
admit it. Admit it. Admit it. Admit it. Admit it.abcAdmit it. Admit it. Come on, admit it. Admit it!
还不是那么无趣
Still not boring.
你知道我会砸瓶子?
did you know I was gonna do that?
我都不知道我会这么干
Because I didn't know Iabcwas gonna do that.
我知道对于失去亲人 你一向处理不好
I know you have trouble losing people.
在新奥尔良abc我见你在会场里带着个快递包裹
In new orleans, I saw you carrying thisabcexpress package around the conference.
既不肯放下 也不愿打开
And you wouldn't let itabcgo,but you wouldn't open it.
我瞧了眼寄件地址
So I peeked at the return address.
Diamond, fairbairn
Diamond, fairbairn.
离婚律师
Divorce attorneys.
你第一任老婆刚递交了离婚协议书
Your first wife had justabcserved you with papers.
你保释我的时候 就知道这些了?
Did you know that when you bailed me out?
是同情我么?
Were you... doing something nice for me?
无聊了找乐子呗
What did I say about being boring?
我们得向你妈妈道歉
We owe your mom an apology.
喂? 是House
Hello? It's House.
气泡测试结果如何?
How'd the bubble test go?
问题不在囊肿 是严重的扩张性心肌病
The problem wasn't the cyst. It'sabcadvanced dilated cardiomyopathy.
做了三维超声 显示在左心房有肿块
We did a three-dimensional echo.abcShowed a mass in the left atrium.
像是心房粘液瘤 但超声图像有些粗糙
looks like an atrial myxoma, but theabcultrasound images are a little grainy,
所以还不好判断
so it's hard to tell.
House?
图像不是粗糙
The images aren't grainy.
看上去确实粗糙
They sure look grainy.
我也见过让你显得高大的照片
I've seen pictures ofabcyou where you look tall.
是铁过度负荷
It's iron overload.
造成图像上的斑点 显得粗糙
Creates speckles on theabcimage,mas it look grainy.
还让她胰腺衰竭 造成血栓和肠道-
Also makes her pancreas fail, herabcblood clot, and her intestine--
心房粘液瘤可能性更大
atrial myxoma is more likely.
做MRI获得更清晰的图像
Mri for a better view.
做完告诉我 你们有多么惭愧abc因为我在500英里外 还比你们瞅得准
And call me back and tell me you're embarrassedabcbecause my eyesight is better 500 miles away.
找个电话号码给我
I need a phone number.
我是新泽西州的医生abc你的一个客户现在由我治
I'm a doctor in newabcjersey,treating one of your clients.
一个寻找亲生父母的年轻女人
A young woman looking forabcher biological parents.
你可以等到MRI结果出来 满足好奇心
You know, you could just wait for theabcmri to have your curiosity satisfied.
你跟我说这些管用么?
What person who is nothingabclike me are you saying that to?
她的父母看起来黑么?
Did the parents look tan?
她得的是遗传病 父母也应该有
The disease she has is genetic,abcwhich means they should have it too.
他们不比其他人更黑
They don't look moreabctan than anyone else.
牙齿变色?
Discolored teeth?
他们是农民 村庄里根本没有牙医
They're farmers--theabcvillage doesn't even have a dentist.
好 谢谢
Right. Thanks.
关系重大的话abc我得说他们不一定是她的父母
But if it matters, I'm notabcconvinced they were her parents.
为什么?
Why not?
他们说他们没有女儿
Because they said they have no daughter.
男的看上去很固执 女的既困惑又害怕
The man was adamant, and the womanabcseemed confused and frightened.
谢谢
Thank you.
鉴别诊断
Differential.
假设你是中年中国妇女
Say you're a middle-agedabcchinese woman...
- 得了吧abc- 说
- fine.abc- Say it.
我是个中年中国妇女
I'm a middle-aged chinese woman.
有个女孩来找你abc说是你多年前分离的女儿
Girl comes to you, says thatabcshe's your long-lost daughter.
你为什么要害怕?
Why would you be frightened?
我害怕是因为她是个威胁?
I'm frightened because she's a threat?
也许她知道什么?
Maybe she knows something?
一出生就再没有见过
She hasn't seen youabcsince she was an infant.
也许是遗产纠纷
Maybe an inheritance issue.
他们是农民
They're peasants.
她的出现是个威胁
Her very presence is a threat.
她是哪年出生的?
She--what year was she born?
83年
'83.
那她不应该活着
She's not supposed to be alive.
中国在1979年实行计划生育
China introduced theabcone-child policy in 1979.
假设他们不想要女孩
Say they didn't want a girl.
试着杀死她
They tried to kill her.
也许婴儿没死 也许父亲惊慌后悔了
Maybe the baby doesn't die. Maybeabcthe father panics or regrets it.
把孩子送到孤儿院 也许他没跟妻子说
Takes the baby to an orphanage.abcMaybe he doesn't tell his wife.
当妻子在25年后看到女孩出现abc还以为是见了鬼
Who freaks out like she's seen a ghostabc25 years later when the girl shows up.
25年前企图谋杀abc会和她现在的健康有什么联系?
Why does attempted murder from 25 years agoabcsuddenly become relevant to her health now?
也许他们对她下毒
Maybe they gave her something toxic.
毒素可能溶于脂肪
It would have to be fat soluble.
这多带劲?
This is fun, isn't it?
让我看MRI图像
Let me see the mri.
没做
We don't have one.
刚想开始扫描 她就呕吐了
She started vomiting asabcsoon as we started the scan.
那就让她边吐边做
Then let her vomit through the mri.
护士用来干什么的
That's what nurses are for.
她父母试过杀死她
Her parents tried to kill her.
不知用什么方式abc但导致她在25年后试着举起佛像时发病
I don't know how, but I know it caused her toabcget sick 25 years later trying to lift a buddha.
解释
Explain.
我跟Wilson讨论过了 现在继续
I already had this conversation withabcwilson--just go with it.
毒药?
Poison?
佛像不会加重病情
Buddha wouldn't make it worse.
也许是重量给背部施压
Maybe the weight stressedabcher back, which--
如果她这辈子没举过重物的话abc还有可能
makes sense if she'sabcnever lifted anything in her life.
她是在第二次试着举起佛像时才发病的
She actually didn't get sick till sheabctried lifting it that second time.
我猜重量改变了
I'm guessing the weight changed.
谁有Taub的呼机号?
Anybody have taub's pager number?
怎么了?
What's up?
给他打个电话
Maybe give him a call.
要是他按了MRI开始键 她就死了
If he tosses that switch onabcthe mri, she's dead.
给她脑袋照X光
X-ray her brain.
钢针
pins.
把它们推进婴儿柔软的卤门
Push them through theabcsoft fontanelle of an infant,
插进脑子里 再用头发盖住入口
you skewer the brain,and theabchair hides the entry wounds.
完美的犯罪
It's the perfect crime.
这些年来她脑子里一直有这些
She's had them in her all these years.
在寺庙里发生了什么变化?
What changed at the temple?
跟MRI中起的变化一样
Same thing that changed in the mri.
令人震惊的是abc不是所有的宗教领袖都是诚实的
shockingly, not all religiousabcleaders are honest.
我猜那些和尚为了欺骗信徒abc在佛像的屁股里塞进一块磁铁
I'm guessing these particular monks are bilkingabcthe faithful by pushing a magnet up buddha's butt.
这张桌子底下也有一块磁石abc根据位置变换会产生吸引和排斥力
There's another one under the table that'llabcrepel or attract,depending on how you shift them.
当她举起磁铁时
When she picked up that magnet,
磁铁移动钢针abc往她大脑的交感神经中枢插得更深
it moved one of the pins deeper into theabcsympathetic nervous center of her brain.
通过神经向她的小肠血管发送信号
This sent a signal through the nerves toabcthe blood vessels in her small intestine
造成在中国以及在MRI大磁铁里的症状
which caused the symptoms in chinaabcand in the giant magnet we call an mri.
她算幸运的
She's lucky.
我们都被她父母耍了
We're all screwed up by our parents.
她有出生文件
She's got documentation.
用手术取出钢针 她会好起来
The pins will be removedabcsurgically, and she'll be fine.
术后会从昏迷中唤醒她
We'll wake her from theabccoma after the operation.
你们能不能别告诉她?
Is there any way you could not tell her?
拜托了 她很脆弱
Please. She's fragile.
她一直渴望了解亲生父母
She desperately wanted toabcknow her biological parents.
要是让她发现他们想她死...
For her to find out thatabcthey wanted her dead...
不知对她打击有多大
I don't know what that'll do to her.
她也许不像你们想的那么脆弱
She may not be as fragile as you think.
我们了解女儿
We know our daughter.
看到这里的钢针
See this pin here?
直接压迫她的成瘾区
It's been pressing directly onabcher addiction center.
不是她的错 也绝不是你们的错
It's not her fault. And it'sabcdefinitely not your fault.
她不是你们想的那样
She's not who you think she is.
听说你的病人没事了
I hear your patient's gonna be all right.
你来为了这个?
Is that why you're here?
问候下同事的病人?
A colleague checking up on a patient?
发生什么事了?
Something goin' on?
我在庆贺
I'm celebrating.
我妈妈也恨他
My mom hated him too.
DNA没有检测出匹配 厉害
Your dna test showed noabcmatch? That's incredible.
你十二岁就发现不是你父亲亲生的?
At the age of 12, you actually figuredabcout your father wasn't your birth father?
这是你想要的结果吧?
That's what you wanted,wasn't it?
为什么让你难受?
Why should it depress you?
不是这让我难受
It doesn't depress me.
什么都没有改变
Doesn't make any difference at all.
这才让我难过
That's what depresses me.
没人能选父母是谁
Well, I guess nobody gets toabcchoose who their parents are.
我甚至不知道 朋友有没有的选
I'm not even sure anymore if weabcget to choose who our friends are.
我跟Cuddy谈过了abc她还没找到人任我的空缺
I spoke with Cuddy. Sheabchasn't filled my position yet.
如果你回来 是因为可怜巴巴的我吸引了你
If you're coming back just because you'reabcattracted to the shine of my neediness...
我倒也能接受
I'd be okay with that.
我回来是因为你是正确的
I'm coming back because you're right.
我们刚做的奇异恼人的旅程abc是Amber死后我最开心的事
That strange, annoying trip we just tookabcwas the most fun I've had since amber died.
你饿了么?
You hungry?
- Wilsonabc- 怎么?
- Wilson.abc- Yeah?
我爸爸死了
My dad's dead.
我很难过
Yeah. My sympathies.